redkawa.com 2017-12-13

# Red Kawa Privacy Policy

Latest Updated: July 22 2011  
Red Kawa is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers Red Kawa's treatment of personally identifiable information that Red Kawa collects when you are on the Red Kawa site, and when you use Red Kawa services. This policy also covers Red Kawa's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Red Kawa's partners share with Red Kawa.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Red Kawa does not own or control, or to people that Red Kawa does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

Red Kawa collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Red Kawa account and when you use certain Red Kawa services. Red Kawa may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.  
When you register with Red Kawa, we ask for several details which may or may not include your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Even though you register with Red Kawa and sign in to our services, you are still anonymous to us.  
Red Kawa also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Red Kawa cookie information and the page you requested. This information is used only for internal purposes by Red Kawa technical support staff.  
Red Kawa uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

It is policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you may provide us, such as through our forum, chat or by email used only for the purposes for which you provide the information. For example, if you choose to give your name and/or any other personal information it is completely by your own will.  
Red Kawa will not solicit or provide any private information to outside vendors or organizations. Information you choose to submit on our site is for public view and at your discretion. Therefore any information you submit publicly on Red Kawa by way of forums or chats can be viewed by outside sources. Any emails submitted to any member of Red Kawa will remain privately held and no such information will be made public unless user permission is granted.

Red Kawa will ONLY send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:  
We have your consent to share the information;  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

**Cookies**

Red Kawa may set and access Red Kawa cookies on your computer.  
Red Kawa allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Red Kawa's cookies.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

Red Kawa gives you the ability to edit your Red Kawa Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Red Kawa to contact you.  
You may request deletion of your Red Kawa account by contacting us here with your account details.

**Security**

Your Red Kawa Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Red Kawa may amend this policy from time to time without prior warning. Please check http://www.redkawa.com/about/privacy.html for the latest version.

**Red Kawa is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of any affiliates or 3rd party organizations displayed within our website.**

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us using this form.
